

MUHAMMAD **UMAIR** +92 316 1755475



Unity Game Developer

umairniazi5556@gmail.com



Pakistan



SUMMARY

I've been making games for two years now, and I'm pretty good at it. People seem to like the games I make, and they often get high ratings on the Play Store. I really enjoy creating fun experiences for players, and I think my skills could be a big help to your game development team.

EDUCATION

Matriculation

FG boys High School no 1 Tariqabad Rawalpindi.

FSC Pre engineering

Manjan Bazam Cadet College Ghazi Campus Tarbela Cantt.

Graduation (BS Computer Science)

Apcoms Affiliated UET Taxila.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Game Development with Unity Game Engine

05 / 2022 - 12 / 2022

MADinc I Shamsabad Murree Road

01 / 2023 - 04 / 2023

7 Vision Tech I Clock tower bahria town phase 7

05 / 2023 - 10 / 2023

Incignite | Gulberg Green Islamabad

05 / 2023 - Present

Ah games studio I bahria town phase 7

PAST PROJECTS

These are some of those Games I made in my career,

- Bull Fighting Game: Bull Games https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.taycoongames.bullfighter.offline.game&hl=en&gl=US Worked on controller, game flow. Worked on size and performance optimization on simulation game.
- Public Bus: Transport Game 2023 https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.inciqnite.bussimulator.busgames.busdrivinggames Worked on RCC controller to make a Bus simulation game, Worked on size and performance optimization.
- Car Parking 3d: Car Games 2023 https://play.qoogle.com/store/apps/details?id=com.funrealms.carparking.games.parking.car.game Worked on RCC controller, level designing, UI implementation.
- $\bullet \ \ Monster\ Truck\ Games-3D\ Stunt\ https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.funrealms.monster.truck.simulator.game$ Worked on RCC controller, level designing, UI implementation.
- Sniper 3D Gun Shooting Games https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.action.game.best.sniper.gun.shooting.games.pure.sniper3d Worked on controller and weapons system.
- Worked on Ludo AI opponents and and it was multiplier on 2D Game.
- Agent Hunt (Working) Working on Agent Hunt game its a spy game and I am working on Player Controller AI and enemy AI.